http://www.parappsys.com/privacy

.
PRIVACY POLICY
This is the privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) for all websites owned and operated by Paragon Application Systems (“PARAGON APPLICATION SYSTEMS” “we” or “our”), including www.paragonedge.com (collectively, the “Service”).
We respect your privacy and appreciate the confidence you have placed in the Service. We are committed to protecting your privacy and preserving your trust. Please carefully review this Privacy Policy to learn about how we collect, use, and protect any personal information you provide us and your choices for managing your personal information. This Privacy Policy is subject to the User Agreement posted on the Service.
We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or wish to exclude your personal information from our direct marketing purposes, please feel free to contact us at: info@paragonedge.com.
You will also always have the option to 'opt-out' of any communications with PARAGON APPLICATION SYSTEMS.
If you would like to update or delete your e-mail address, mailing address or other personal information with us please contact us the same way.
We collect information from our users at several different points on the Service. For example, we may collect personally identifiable information from you such as your name, address, phone number, and e-mail address when you register, subscribe to one of our services, enter sweepstakes, contests or other promotions offered by or through the Service, and at other times.
In addition, we automatically collect non-personal information such as your browser type, operating system, IP address, and Service usage information, in order to, among other things, evaluate and improve the performance of the Service.
We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose personally identifiable information to third parties, without your explicit permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
We collect and use information for internal purposes, such as:
enhancing your experience at the Service;
performing administration and technical support for the Service;
performing administration and technical support for the Service;
enabling you to enter sweepstakes, contests and other promotions;
creating aggregate information and analytics about demographics and usage patterns;
inviting our promotional vendors and advertisers—with your explicit permission—to call to your attention special offers, products and services that may be of interest to you.
enabling purchases of goods and services
We may use aggregate information to measure general Service usage patterns and characteristics of our user base, and we may include such aggregate information about our audience in reports to our commercial vendors. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, a certain percentage of our users live in a certain area) without your permission in order to describe our audience to existing and prospective advertisers or other third parties. However, this aggregate information does not reference names, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, or other personally identifiable information, and it is not traceable to a specific recipient or user e-mail address.
We also may share personal information with companies affiliated with PARAGON APPLICATION SYSTEMS. In the event that PARAGON APPLICATION SYSTEMS is merged, or in the event of a transfer of our assets, we may disclose or transfer your personal information in connection with such transaction. In the event of such a transfer, we will notify you of the change of control of your personal information. You should also be aware that bankruptcy courts of equity may have the authority, under certain circumstances, to permit your personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission.
From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours. For example, we may contract with service providers to provide certain services including credit card processing, data management, promotional services, etc. We provide our service providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each service provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of your information in order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification or disclosure.
Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to PARAGON APPLICATION SYSTEMS or its affiliates, or to others. We may also disclose your personal information when we believe the law requires it.
The general registration area can be found on the Service home page and at other locations throughout the Service. To use or access certain features of the Service, you may have to register or otherwise provide personal information. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you elect not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to access certain content or features or participate in various areas of the Service.
We use encryption and authentication tools when appropriate to protect the security of personal information that you share with us. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect personal information, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the Service, and you do so at your own risk.
We may place a text file called a “cookie” in the browser files of your computer or use other technology to improve your navigation of the Service. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your Web browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Generally, we use cookies to remind us of who you are, tailor our products and services to suit your personal interests, estimate our audience size, track your status in our sweepstakes, contests, and promotions and/or analyze your visiting patterns. The use of cookies is an industry standard; you will find them at most major Web sites. Cookies make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your preferences while you are using the Service. For this reason, we may save passwords, credit card or other personal information in cookies. You can generally set your Web browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. If you set your Web browser not to accept cookies, it may affect your ability to utilize all features on the Service.
The Service may contain links to Web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked Web sites may be different from our Privacy Policy. You access such linked Web sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked Web site before disclosing any personal information on such site.
Our online chat areas, bulletin boards, other public forums and user-generated content (i.e., photos, videos) can be a useful way for you to express yourself to other online users. When you post messages or otherwise use these features, the information that you provide (including personally identifiable information) may be publicly available to, collected by, and used by third parties. We are not responsible for the content of messages or images posted by users or disclosures of personal information.
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. Because we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we also do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting the changed Privacy Policy here. Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of the Service and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent.
Last updated: May 25th, 2018
ATM Testing
Automation
Certification
Performance
Web FASTest
VirtualATM
Support
World Headquarters326 Raleigh StreetHolly Springs, NC 27540 +1-919-567-9890
Copyright © 2020 All Rights Reserved by Paragon Application Systems | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
